hostingshouse.com 2016-10-30

# Privacy Policy - Hostings House

By visiting our website and availing yourself of our services, you allow us to process personal data submitted by you in ways and for reasons given below. 

1) The following data about you may be collected and processed: details pertaining to the transactions made through our website; information required for fulfilling your order; information for contacting you which includes your name, email address, residential and office address, and phone number; data related to payments; when you contact us we can save the record of our correspondence; if cardholder is some other member belonging to your household we can collect information regarding that person as well. 

2) Your information is used by us for various purposes: identifying you and your accounts with us; reviewing and improving our site and services; providing customer care; carrying out marketing; performing statistical analysis; updating you about changes in our services and website; for informing you about products and services you have already purchased or might want to acquire in future, provided you have given your consent to receiving such updates. 

3) Your personal information may be disclosed to third parties: a cardholder purchasing services on your behalf; our employees or agents involved in providing you certain services or managing your accounts; companies having business partnerships with us or working with us; in case a third party acquires some or all of our assets or buys some of our business we will make them enter formal confidentiality undertakings with regard to your personal information; in case we have to comply with some legal obligation or secure some business interest such as avoiding frauds, minimizing risks and resolving disputes. 

4) Cookies are used by us for various reasons, for instance, when you sign up with us for a particular package or register your domain name, we are able to track your information through cookies. However, cookies are not used for tracking individual information and only HostingsHouse will be able to access its cookies. When you log on to our website cookies will be issued by our system. You can choose to refuse accepting cookies by changing your browser setting relevant to the cookies feature but that might restrict your access to certain parts of our website and keep you from carrying out certain transactions. We cannot know and neither are we interested in knowing the identities of people who simply visit our site. 

5) We store all the information you have provided us on our secured servers in the US. Credit card numbers are only used for payment processing, all transactions being encrypted, and won’t be used for the purpose of marketing. 

It is your responsibility to keep the password you use to access our website fully confidential, you must not share your password with anyone. When we receive information from you, we will do our best to prevent unauthorized access by implementing strict security procedures, though we do not guarantee your personal information to be absolutely secure. Once your personal information has been transmitted to our system the responsibility will rest with you transmission through the internet is by no means completely secure. 

6) HostingsHouse can give links to third party sites. Before you share any information with these third party sites we advise you to have a look at their privacy policies as we do not have any control over them. 

7) We seek your assistance in helping us maintain the accuracy of information you have given by informing us of any changes to your title, address, phone number or e-mail address. We have the right to make periodic revisions of our privacy policy and whenever that happens we will inform you of the changes. However, your personal information will be subject to that version of our privacy policy which was in effect at the time when you sent us your data. 

8) When we use your personal data for marketing purposes or have to share it with some third party for the same purpose, we will inform you in advance. You have the right to convey your disapproval and deny us such use of your personal data by e-mailing us 

Contact Us

If you have any questions or comments related to privacy send them in [privacy@hostingshouse.com](mailto:privacy@hostingshouse.com)

Please Note: when you choose HostingsHouse as your service provider you agree to be bound by all of its terms and conditions.
